Guide to the Gerald H. Anderson Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Writings, Lectures, Research Files, 1957-2012; Series II
  - Regarding booklength works
    - Biographical Dictionary of Christian Mission
      - Articles File
        - Bolanos, Luis de (Box 7, Folder 714)
        - Bolotov, Ioasaph (Box 7, Folder 715)
        - Bolshakoff, Serge (Box 7, Folder 716)
        - Bompas, William (Box 7, Folder 717)
        - Bonaventura de Sardegna (Box 7, Folder 718)
        - Bondolfi, Pietro (Box 7, Folder 719)
        - Boniface (Box 7, Folder 720)
        - Bonjean, Ernst Christophe (Box 7, Folder 721)
        - Bonnand, Clement (Box 7, Folder 722)
        - Boone, William Jones (Box 7, Folder 723)
        - Booth, Ballington and Maud (Charlesworth) (Box 7, Folder 724)
        - Booth, Catherine Mumford (Box 7, Folder 725)
        - Booth, Evangeline Cory (Box 7, Folder 726)
        - Booth, Joseph (Box 7, Folder 727)
        - Booth, William (Box 7, Folder 728)
        - Booth-Tucker, Frederick and Emma (Moss) (Box 7, Folder 729)
        - Borden, William Whiting (Box 7, Folder 730)
        - Borgeoys, Marguerite (Box 7, Folder 731)
        - Borghero, Francesco (Box 7, Folder 732)
        - Boris I (Box 7, Folder 733)
        - Borrow, George (Box 7, Folder 734)
        - Bosch, David Jacobus (Box 7, Folder 735)
        - Bosco, Giovanni (John) (Box 7, Folder 736)
        - Bosshardt, Alfred (Box 7, Folder 737)
        - Boudinot, Elias (Galagina) (Box 7, Folder 738)
        - Bouey, Elizabeth Coles (Box 7, Folder 739)
        - Bouvet, Joachim (Box 7, Folder 740)
        - Bowen, George (Box 7, Folder 741)
        - Bowen, Thomas Jefferson (Box 7, Folder 742)
        - Bowley, William (Box 7, Folder 743)
        - Bowman, Robert H. (Box 7, Folder 744)
        - Boyce, William Binnington (Box 7, Folder 745)
        - Boyl (Boil, Buil, Buyl), Bernal (Bernardo) (Box 7, Folder 746)
        - Braden, Charles Samuel (Box 7, Folder 747)
        - Bradley, Daniel Beach (Box 7, Folder 748)
        - Braide, Garrick (Box 7, Folder 749)
        - Brainard, David (Box 7, Folder 750)
        - Brainerd, John (Box 7, Folder 751)
        - Braisted, Paul and Ruth (Box 7, Folder 752)
        - Brancati de Laurea, Lawrence (Box 7, Folder 753)
        - Brand, Evelyn (Box 7, Folder 754)
        - Brand, Paul (Box 7, Folder 755)
        - Braun, Peter (Box 7, Folder 756)
        - Bray, Thomas (Box 7, Folder 757)
        - Brebeuf, Jean de (Box 7, Folder 758)
        - Brechter, Suso (Box 7, Folder 759)
        - Breck, James Lloyd (Box 7, Folder 760)
        - Breda, Gregorius van (Box 7, Folder 761)
        - Brennecke, Gerhard (Box 7, Folder 762)
        - Brent, Charles Henry (Box 7, Folder 763)
        - Bresillac, Melchior Marie Joseph de (Box 7, Folder 764)
        - Breton, Raymond (Box 7, Folder 765)
        - Brett, William Henry (Box 7, Folder 766)
        - Bridgman, Eiljah Colman (Box 7, Folder 767)
        - Bridgman, Eliza Jane Gillett (Box 7, Folder 768)
        - Bright, William ('Bill') Rohl (Box 7, Folder 769)
        - Britto, Joao de (Box 7, Folder 770)
        - Brockman, Fletcher (Box 7, Folder 771)
        - Broger, John (Box 7, Folder 772)
        - Bromilow, William (Box 7, Folder 773)
        - Bronson, Miles (Box 7, Folder 774)
        - Brooke, Graham Wilmont (Box 7, Folder 775)
        - Bronnum, Niels Huegh (Box 7, Folder 776)
        - Broomhall, Anthony James (Box 7, Folder 777)
        - Broomhall, Benjamin (Box 7, Folder 778)
        - Broomhall, Marshall (Box 7, Folder 779)
        - Broughton, William Grant (Box 7, Folder 780)
        - Brown, Alfred Nesbit (Box 7, Folder 781)
        - Brown, Arthur Judson (Box 7, Folder 782)
        - Brown, David (Box 7, Folder 783)
        - Brown, Edith (Box 7, Folder 784)
        - Brown, George (Box 7, Folder 785)
        - Brown, Lawrence (Box 7, Folder 786)
        - Brown, Nathan (Box 7, Folder 787)
        - Brown, Samuel R. (Box 8, Folder 788)
        - Browne, Stanley George (Box 8, Folder 789)
        - Brownlee, John (Box 8, Folder 790)
        - Brubaker, Henry H. (Box 8, Folder 791)
        - Bruckner, Gottlieb (Box 8, Folder 792)
        - Bruillard, Philibert de (Box 8, Folder 793)
        - Bruno of Querfurt (Box 8, Folder 794)
        - Brunton, Henry (Box 8, Folder 795)
        - Bucer, Martin (Box 8, Folder 796)
        - Buchan, Jane (Box 8, Folder 797)
        - Buchanan, Claudius (Box 8, Folder 798)
        - Buchner, Charles (Box 8, Folder 799)
        - Buck, Pearl S. (Box 8, Folder 800)
        - Buglio, Ludovico (Box 8, Folder 801)
        - Buhlmann, Walbert (Box 8, Folder 802)
        - Builes, Miguel Angel (Box 8, Folder 803)
        - Buker, Raymond Bates (Box 8, Folder 804)
        - Bulmer, John (Box 8, Folder 805)
        - Bulu (Mbulu), Joeli (Box 8, Folder 806)
        - Buntain, Mark (Box 8, Folder 807)
        - Burgess, Paul (Pablo) and Dora (Box 8, Folder 808)
        - Burns, William Chalmers (Box 8, Folder 809)
        - Burton, John Wear (Box 8, Folder 810)
        - Burton, William Frederick Padwick (Box 8, Folder 811)
        - Buss, Ernst (Box 8, Folder 812)
        - Butler, Elizur (Elihu?) (Box 8, Folder 813)
        - Butler, Fanny Jane (Box 8, Folder 814)
        - Butler, William and Clementina (Box 8, Folder 815)
        - Buxton, Alfred (Box 8, Folder 816)
        - Buxton, Godfrey (Box 8, Folder 817)
        - Buxton, Barclay Fowell (Box 8, Folder 818)
        - Buxton, Thomas Fowell (Box 8, Folder 819)
        - Buzacot, Aaron (Box 8, Folder 820)
        - Byington, Cyrus (Box 8, Folder 821)
        - Cable, Alice Mildred (Box 8, Folder 822)
        - Cabral, Francisco (Box 8, Folder 823)
        - Cabrini, (Mother) Frances Xavier (Box 8, Folder 824)
        - Caffray, D. Willia (Box 8, Folder 825)
        - Cairns, David Smith (Box 8, Folder 826)
        - Cakobau (Thakombau) (Box 8, Folder 827)
        - Calder, Helen B. (Box 8, Folder 828)
        - Caldwell, Robert (Box 8, Folder 829)
        - Calhoun, Simeon Howard (Box 8, Folder 830)
        - Callaway, Henry (Box 8, Folder 831)
        - Callenberg, Johann Heinrich (Box 8, Folder 832)
        - Calverley, Edwin (Box 8, Folder 833)
        - Calvert, James (Box 8, Folder 834)
        - Calvin, John (Box 8, Folder 835)
        - Camara, (Dom) Helder Pessoa (Box 8, Folder 836)
        - Cambridge Seven (Box 8, Folder 837)
        - Campbell, John (Box 8, Folder 838)
        - Camphor, Alexander Priestly (Box 8, Folder 839)
        - Camps, Arnulf (Box 8, Folder 840)
        - Cancer, Luis (Box 8, Folder 841)
        - Candidius, Georgius (Box 8, Folder 842)
        - Canut, J.B. (Box 8, Folder 843)
        - Capaddose Abraham (Box 8, Folder 844)
        - Capers, William (Box 8, Folder 845)
        - Capillas, Francisco Ferdinando de (Box 8, Folder 846)
        - Capitein, Jacobus Elisa Joannes (Box 8, Folder 847)
        - Cardoso, Mattheus (Box 8, Folder 848)
        - Carey, Charotte Emilia (Ruhmohr) (Box 8, Folder 849)
        - Carey, Felix (Box 8, Folder 850)
        - Carey (Cary) Lott (Box 8, Folder 851)
        - Carey, William (Box 8, Folder 852)
        - Cargill, David and Margaret (Smith) (Box 8, Folder 853)
        - Carlson, Paul (Box 8, Folder 854)
        - Carmichael, Amy Beatrice (Wilson) (Box 8, Folder 855)
        - Carneiro (also Carnero), Melchior (Box 8, Folder 856)
        - Carpenter, Chapin Howard (Box 8, Folder 857)
        - Carroll, John (Box 8, Folder 858)
        - Carver, William Owen (Box 8, Folder 859)
        - Cary, Maude (Box 8, Folder 860)
        - Casalis, Eugene (Box 8, Folder 861)
        - Case, Isaac (Box 8, Folder 862)
        - Case, William (Box 8, Folder 863)
        - Cash, Willliam Wilson (Box 8, Folder 864)
        - Caspari, Carl Paul (Box 8, Folder 865)
        - Castro, Emilio (Box 8, Folder 866)
        - Cassels, William wharton (Box 8, Folder 867)
        - Castiglione, Giuseppe (Box 8, Folder 868)
        - Castro, Matthew de (Box 8, Folder 869)
        - Catalani, Jordan (Box 8, Folder 870)
        - Cattaneo, Lazzaro (Box 8, Folder 871)
        - Cavazzi da montecuccolo (Box 8, Folder 872)
        - Cespedes, Gregorio de (Box 8, Folder 873)
        - Chabanel, Noel (Box 8, Folder 874)
        - Chakkarai, V(engal) (Box 8, Folder 875)
        - Chakko, Sarah (Box 8, Folder 876)
        - Chalmers, James (Box 8, Folder 877)
        - Chamers, John (Box 8, Folder 878)
        - Chalmers, Thomas (Box 8, Folder 879)
        - Chamberlain, Jacob (Box 8, Folder 880)
        - Chamberlain, John (Box 8, Folder 881)
        - Chaminade, Guillaume Joseph (Box 8, Folder 882)
        - Champagnat, Marcellin Joseph Benoit (Box 8, Folder 883)
        - chandran, J(oshua) (Box 8, Folder 884)
        - Chanel, Pierre Louis Marie (Box 8, Folder 885)
        - Chang (Box 8, Folder 886)
        - Chang Barnabas (Box 8, Folder 887)
        - chao, T(su)- C(h'en) (Box 8, Folder 888)
        - chapdelaine, Auguste (Box 8, Folder 889)
        - Chappotin de Neuville, Helene de (Box 8, Folder 890)
        - Charles, Pierre (Box 8, Folder 891)
        - Chatterjee, K(ali) C(haran) (Box 8, Folder 892)
        - chatterton, Percy (Box 8, Folder 893)
        - Chaumont, Denis (Box 8, Folder 894)
        - Chavara, Kuriackos Elias (Box 8, Folder 895)
        - Chavoin, Jeanne Marie (Mother St. Joseph) (Box 8, Folder 896)
        - Chawner, C. Austin (Box 8, Folder 897)
        - Cheek, Landon N(apoleon) (Box 8, Folder 898)
        - Cheese, John Ethelstan (Box 8, Folder 899)
        - Chen, Wen Yuen (Box 8, Folder 900)
        - Chenchiah, P(andipedi) (Box 8, Folder 901)
        - Cheng, Ching-Yi (Box 8, Folder 902)
        - Chesterman, Clement C. (Box 8, Folder 903)
        - Chestnut, Eleanor (Box 8, Folder 904)
        - Chevalier, Jules (Box 9, Folder 905)
        - Chi-oang (Box 9, Folder 906)
        - Child, Abbie B. (Box 9, Folder 907)
        - Chilembwe, John (Box 9, Folder 908)
        - Ching Tien-Yin (Jing Dianying) (Box 9, Folder 909)
        - Chisholm, Caroline (Box 9, Folder 910)
        - Chitambar, Jaswant Rao (Box 9, Folder 911)
        - Choi, John (Box 9, Folder 912)
        - Cheng Yak-Jong, Augustine (Box 9, Folder 913)
        - Chou, Wen-mo (Portugese name Vellozo) (Box 9, Folder 914)
        - Chou, Wen Mo (Box 9, Folder 915)
        - Chotuncevskij, Joasaf (Box 9, Folder 916)
        - Christaller, Johannes Gottlieb (Box 9, Folder 917)
        - Christlieb, Theodor (Box 9, Folder 918)
        - Christie, Dugald (Box 9, Folder 919)
        - Christoffel. Ernst J. (Box 9, Folder 920)
        - Chrysostom, John (Box 9, Folder 921)
        - Church, J. E. (Box 9, Folder 922)
        - Claret, Antonius Maria (Box 9, Folder 923)
        - Clark, Charles Allen (Box 9, Folder 924)
        - Clark, Ephraim W. (Box 9, Folder 925)
        - Clark, Henry Martyn (Box 9, Folder 926)
        - Clark, Robert (Box 9, Folder 927)
        - Clark, William Smith (Box 9, Folder 928)
        - Clarke, John (Box 9, Folder 929)
        - Classe, Leon (Box 9, Folder 930)
        - Claver, Peter (Box 9, Folder 931)
        - Clement VIII (Ippolito Aldobrandini) (Box 9, Folder 932)
        - Clement XI (Giovani Francesco Albani) (Box 9, Folder 933)
        - Clement of Ochard (ohrid) (Box 9, Folder 934)
        - Clifford, James (Box 9, Folder 935)
        - Clough, John Everett and Emma R. (Box 9, Folder 936)
        - Coan, Titus (Box 9, Folder 937)
        - Coates, Dandeson (Box 9, Folder 938)
        - Cobo, Bernabe (Box 9, Folder 939)
        - Cochran, Joseph Plumb (Box 9, Folder 940)
        - Coccejus, Johnanes (Box 9, Folder 941)
        - Cochran, George (Box 9, Folder 942)
        - Cochran, Joseph Gallup (Box 9, Folder 943)
        - Cochrane, Thomas (Box 9, Folder 944)
        - Codrington, Robert Henry (Box 9, Folder 945)
        - Coe, Shoki (C. H. Hwang) (Box 9, Folder 946)
        - Coerper, Heinrich Wilhelm (Box 9, Folder 947)
        - Coillard, Francoise (Box 9, Folder 948)
        - Coke, Thomas (Box 9, Folder 949)
        - Coker, Daniel (Box 9, Folder 950)
        - Colenso, Elizabeth (Box 9, Folder 951)
        - Colenso, john william (Box 9, Folder 952)
        - Colin, Jean Claude Marie (Box 9, Folder 953)
        - Colley, William W. (Box 9, Folder 954)
        - Collins, J. (Box 9, Folder 955)
        - Columba (Box 9, Folder 956)
        - Columban (also Columbanus) (Box 9, Folder 957)
        - Comber, Thomas (Box 9, Folder 958)
        - Commenius, Johanne Amos (Box 9, Folder 959)
        - Comboni, Daniele (Box 9, Folder 960)
        - Condit, Azubah (Box 9, Folder 961)
        - Conforti, Guido Maria (Box 9, Folder 962)
        - Congar, Yves (Box 9, Folder 963)
        - Considine, John J. (Box 9, Folder 964)
        - constantine the Great (Box 9, Folder 965)
        - Constantine, Cyril (Box 9, Folder 966)
        - Cook, Albert Ruskin (Box 9, Folder 967)
        - Cook, Eulalia (Box 9, Folder 968)
        - Cook, J.A.B. (Box 9, Folder 969)
        - Cook, Gonzalez, Eulalia (Box 9, Folder 971)
        - Cooke, Spohie (Box 9, Folder 972)
        - Coolen, Coenraad Laurens (Box 9, Folder 973)
        - Combs, Lucinda (Box 9, Folder 974)
        - Cope, Marianne (Box 9, Folder 975)
        - Copleston, R.S. (Box 9, Folder 976)
        - Coppin, Fanny and Levi (Box 9, Folder 977)
        - Corbett, Hunter (Box 9, Folder 978)
        - Corbinian (Box 9, Folder 979)
        - Cordoba, Pedro de (Box 9, Folder 980)
        - Corrado, Alejandro (Box 9, Folder 981)
        - Corrie, Daniel (Box 9, Folder 982)
        - Costantini, Celso (Box 9, Folder 983)
        - Costas, Orlando E. (Box 9, Folder 984)
        - Cotta, Antony (Box 9, Folder 985)
        - Cotton, George Edward Lynch (Box 9, Folder 986)
        - Coudrin, Pierre Marie Joseph (Box 9, Folder 987)
        - Coughlan, Laurence (Box 9, Folder 988)
        - Couplet, Philippe (Box 9, Folder 989)
        - Courveille, Jean Claude (Box 9, Folder 990)
        - Cousin, William E(dward) (Box 9, Folder 991)
        - Courvreur, Seraphin (Box 9, Folder 992)
        - Cowman, Lettie Burd and Charles Elmer (Box 9, Folder 993)
        - Cox, Melville Beveridge (Box 9, Folder 994)
        - Cragg, A(lbert) Keneth (Box 9, Folder 995)
        - Crawford, Daniel (Box 9, Folder 996)
        - Crawford, Isabelle (Box 9, Folder 997)
        - Crawford, T(arleton) P(erry) (Box 9, Folder 998)
        - Creux, Ernest (Box 9, Folder 999)
        - Criminal, Antoine (Box 9, Folder 1000)
        - Cripps, Arthurs Shearly (Box 9, Folder 1001)
        - Crook, William Pascoe (Box 9, Folder 1002)
        - Crosby, Aaron (Box 9, Folder 1003)
        - Crosby, Thomas (Box 9, Folder 1004)
        - Cross, William (Box 9, Folder 1005)
        - Crowe, Frederick (Box 9, Folder 1006)
        - Crowther, Dandeson Coates (Box 9, Folder 1007)
        - Crowther, Samuel Adjai (Box 9, Folder 1008)
        - Crumwell, Alexander (Box 9, Folder 1009)
        - Cust, Rubert Needham (Box 9, Folder 1010)
        - Cushing, Ellen Howard (Box 9, Folder 1011)
        - Cushing, Richard James (Box 9, Folder 1012)
        - Cuthbert (Box 9, Folder 1013)
        - Da Costa, Isaac (Box 10, Folder 1014)
        - Da Rocha, Joao (Box 10, Folder 1015)
        - Dablon, Claude (Box 10, Folder 1016)
        - Dahl, Otto Christian (Box 10, Folder 1017)
        - Dahle, Lars Nilsen (Box 10, Folder 1018)
        - Dake, Vivian Adelbert (Box 10, Folder 1019)
        - Dalle Perier, Luis (Box 10, Folder 1020)
        - Dalman, Gustaf (Box 10, Folder 1021)
        - Dalmien of Molokai (Joseph Damien de Veuster0 (Box 10, Folder 1022)
        - Dammann, Ernst (Box 10, Folder 1023)
        - Danbolt, Erling (Box 10, Folder 1024)
        - Dandoy, G. (Box 10, Folder 1025)
        - Daniel, Anthony (Box 10, Folder 1026)
        - Danielou, Jean (Box 10, Folder 1027)
        - Dannie, Thomas John (Box 10, Folder 1028)
        - Darling, David (Box 10, Folder 1029)
        - Darling, Thomas Young (Box 10, Folder 1030)
        - Daeuble, Carl Gustav (Box 10, Folder 1031)
        - Datta, S(urendra) K(umara) (Box 10, Folder 1032)
        - Daubanton, Francoise Elbertus (Box 10, Folder 1033)
        - David, Christian (Box 10, Folder 1034)
        - Davidson, Andrew (Box 10, Folder 1035)
        - Davidson, H. Frances (Box 10, Folder 1036)
        - Davidson, Benjamin (Box 10, Folder 1037)
        - Davies, John (Box 10, Folder 1038)
        - Davis, John Merle (Box 10, Folder 1039)
        - Day, David A. (Box 10, Folder 1040)
        - Day, George Edward (Box 10, Folder 1041)
        - Day, John (Box 10, Folder 1042)
        - Day, Samuel Stearns (Box 10, Folder 1043)
        - Dean, William (Box 10, Folder 1044)
        - D'Elia, Pasquale (Box 10, Folder 1045)
        - Deck, Northcote (Box 10, Folder 1046)
        - Dehaqani- Tafti, Hassan Barnabas (Box 10, Folder 1047)
        - Dehergne, Joseph (Box 10, Folder 1048)
        - Delaney, Emma Bertha (Box 10, Folder 1049)
        - Delitzsch, Franz Julius (Box 10, Folder 1050)
        - De Menasce, Pierre Jean (Box 10, Folder 1051)
        - De Rougemont, Francois (Box 10, Folder 1052)
        - De Silva, Lynn A (Box 10, Folder 1053)
        - De Smet, Pierre Jean (Box 10, Folder 1054)
        - Dengel, Anna (Box 10, Folder 1055)
        - Dennis, Thomas John (Box 10, Folder 1056)
        - Dennis (Box 10, Folder 1057)
        - Dennis, James Shepard (Box 10, Folder 1058)
        - Depelchin, Henri (Box 10, Folder 1059)
        - Desideri, Hippolytus (Box 10, Folder 1060)
        - Devanandan, Paul David (Box 10, Folder 1061)
        - Devasahaym, John (Box 10, Folder 1062)
        - Dey, Lal Behari (Box 10, Folder 1063)
        - Deyneka, Peter (Box 10, Folder 1064)
        - Dick, Amos Daniel Maurice (Box 10, Folder 1065)
        - Deyneka, Peter (Box 10, Folder 1066)
        - Dickson, James and Lillian (Box 10, Folder 1067)
        - Dindinger, Johannes (Box 10, Folder 1068)
        - DirksHeinrich (Box 10, Folder 1069)
        - Doane, Edward Topping (Box 10, Folder 1070)
        - Dober, Johann Leonhard (Box 10, Folder 1071)
        - Dobinson, Henry Hughes (Box 10, Folder 1072)
        - Dobrizhoffer, Martin (Box 10, Folder 1073)
        - Dodge, Grace Hoadley (Box 10, Folder 1074)
        - Dodge, Ralph E. (Box 10, Folder 1075)
        - Doig, Andrew (Box 10, Folder 1076)
        - Doke, C. M. (Box 10, Folder 1077)
        - Doke, Joseph James (Box 10, Folder 1078)
        - Doll, Ludwig (Box 10, Folder 1079)
        - Dole, Charlotte Knapp (Box 10, Folder 1080)
        - Dominic (Box 10, Folder 1081)
        - Donaldson, Dwight (Box 10, Folder 1082)
        - Donders, Peter (Box 10, Folder 1083)
        - Donshoy, Vladimir (Box 10, Folder 1084)
        - Dooley, Thomas A. (Box 10, Folder 1085)
        - Doremus, Sarah (Box 10, Folder 1086)
        - Douglas, Carstairs (Box 10, Folder 1087)
        - D'orville, Albert (Box 10, Folder 1088)
        - Draper, Minnie Tingley (Box 10, Folder 1089)
        - Draskoczy, Laszlo (Box 10, Folder 1090)
        - Drexel, Katherine (Box 10, Folder 1091)
        - Drebert, Ferdinand (Box 10, Folder 1092)
        - Droese Ernest (Box 10, Folder 1093)
        - Druilletes (or Dreuillette), Gabriel (Box 10, Folder 1094)
        - Drummond, Henry (Box 10, Folder 1095)
        - Dubois, Jean Antoine (Box 10, Folder 1096)
        - Dubose, Hampden Coit (Box 10, Folder 1097)
        - Dchesne, Rose Philippine (Box 10, Folder 1098)
        - Duff, Alexander (Box 10, Folder 1099)
        - Dufresse, Jean-Gabriel- Taurin (Box 10, Folder 1100)
        - Duncan, John (Box 10, Folder 1101)
        - Duncan, william (Box 10, Folder 1102)
        - Dunger, George Albert (Box 10, Folder 1103)
        - Duparquet, Charles (Box 10, Folder 1104)
        - De Plessis, David (Box 10, Folder 1105)
        - Du Plessis, J. D. (Box 10, Folder 1106)
        - Durr, Johannes (Box 10, Folder 1107)
        - Dutton, Ira Barnes (Box 10, Folder 1108)
        - Dwane, James Mata (Box 10, Folder 1109)
        - Dwane, James M. (Box 10, Folder 1110)
        - Dwight, H.G.O (Box 10, Folder 1111)
        - Dyer, Jack (Box 10, Folder 1112)
        - Dyer, John (Box 10, Folder 1113)
        - Dyer, Samuel (Box 10, Folder 1114)
        - Eastman, Eliane Goodale (Box 10, Folder 1115)
        - Eastman, George (Box 10, Folder 1116)
        - Edersheim, Alfred (Box 10, Folder 1117)
        - Eddy, G(eorge) Sherwood (Box 10, Folder 1118)
        - Eddy, Mary P. (Box 10, Folder 1119)
        - Edkins, Joseph (Box 10, Folder 1120)
        - Edmiston, Alethea Brown (Box 10, Folder 1121)
        - Edwards, Jonathan (Box 10, Folder 1122)
        - Edwards, Mary kelley (Box 10, Folder 1123)
        - Edwins, August (Box 10, Folder 1124)
        - Egede, Hans (Box 10, Folder 1125)
        - Ehrenfeuchter, Friedrich (Box 11, Folder 1126)
        - Eligius (Box 11, Folder 1127)
        - Eliot, John (Box 11, Folder 1128)
        - Elliott, Benjamin Franklin (Box 11, Folder 1129)
        - Ellinwood F. F. (Box 11, Folder 1130)
        - Elliot, James (Box 11, Folder 1131)
        - Elliott, Walter (Box 11, Folder 1132)
        - Ellis, William and Mary Mercy (Box 11, Folder 1133)
        - Elmslie, Walter Augus (Box 11, Folder 1134)
        - Elmslie, William and Margaret (Duncan) (Box 11, Folder 1135)
        - Elwin, Verrier (Box 11, Folder 1136)
        - Ely, Mary and [Sister] Charlotte (Box 11, Folder 1137)
        - Emde, Johannes (Box 11, Folder 1138)
        - Emmerich, Heinrich (Box 11, Folder 1139)
        - Enbaqom (Box 11, Folder 1140)
        - England, John (Box 11, Folder 1141)
        - Epalle, Jean-Baptiste (Box 11, Folder 1142)
        - Erasmus, Desiderius (Box 11, Folder 1143)
        - Errico, Gaetano Cosma Damiano (Box 11, Folder 1144)
        - Eto, Silas (Box 11, Folder 1145)
        - Eulogius (Box 11, Folder 1146)
        - Eusebius (Box 11, Folder 1147)
        - Evald, Emmy (Box 11, Folder 1148)
        - Evans, James (Box 11, Folder 1149)
        - Evans, R. M. (Box 11, Folder 1150)
        - Evans, Robert (Box 11, Folder 1151)
        - Evarts, Jeremiah (Box 11, Folder 1152)
        - Ewing, Greville (Box 11, Folder 1153)
        - Ewing, James C.R (Box 11, Folder 1154)
        - Ezana (Box 11, Folder 1155)
        - Frabri, Friedrich (Box 11, Folder 1156)
        - Frabricius, Johann Philipp (Box 11, Folder 1157)
        - Falkner, Thomas (Box 11, Folder 1158)
        - Farquhar, John Nicol (Box 11, Folder 1159)
        - Farrington, Sophronia (Box 11, Folder 1160)
        - Faulding, Jenny (Box 11, Folder 1161)
        - Favier, Pierre-Marie Alphonse (Box 11, Folder 1162)
        - Feild, Edward (Box 11, Folder 1163)
        - Feller, Henriette Odin (Box 11, Folder 1164)
        - Fenn, C. C. (Box 11, Folder 1165)
        - Ferguson, Abby (Box 11, Folder 1166)
        - Ferguson, Samuel David (Box 11, Folder 1167)
        - Fenbaugh, Hettie (Box 11, Folder 1168)
        - Fielde, Adele M. (Box 11, Folder 1169)
        - Figurovskij, Innokentij (Box 11, Folder 1170)
        - Fisch, Rudolf (Box 11, Folder 1171)
        - Fisher, George (Box 11, Folder 1172)
        - Fisher, Welthy Honsinger (Box 11, Folder 1173)
        - Fisk, Pliny (Box 11, Folder 1174)
        - Fiske, Fidelia (Box 11, Folder 1175)
        - Fitch, George A. (Box 11, Folder 1176)
        - Fison, Lorimer (Box 11, Folder 1177)
        - Fjellstedt, Peter (Box 11, Folder 1178)
        - Flad, Johann Martin (Box 11, Folder 1179)
        - Fleming, Daniel Johnson (Box 11, Folder 1180)
        - Fleming, Archibald Lang (Box 11, Folder 1181)
        - Fleming, John (Box 11, Folder 1182)
        - Fleming, Louise (Lulu) (Box 11, Folder 1183)
        - Fleming, Peter (Box 11, Folder 1184)
        - Fleming, Paul william (Box 11, Folder 1185)
        - Fliedner, Federico (Box 11, Folder 1186)
        - Florovsky, Georges Vasilievich (Box 11, Folder 1187)